YEAH.
i spit raps like a heart attack. fast fatal heart impact
Past painful scars in fact, I blast tasteful bars in packs
I back up my actions, fact, don't ask, grab reactions, jacked
Attack with every word then act with class, as they hear me snap
I got nothing to lose, 'cause I fought and felt the bruise
Now I'm not the one confused, call the shots and they produce
I ain't lost I'm finally loose, pick a noose over excuse
I need the views to boost me to a new abuse of being used
Everybody wants a piece now, y'all can rest in peace now
Your dead to me so peace out, remember your discrete doubt
Get ready for defeat now, I'm gon' make you bleed out
Listen on repeat now and weed out all the weak now
Get up and make a change, don't remember yesterday
If you got something to say, speak your mind before your grave
'cause your life is yours to save, ain't nobody gonna change
Everybody stays the same, so be different, make a name, huh?
And just like a soldier
I keep on moving forward
Always getting closer
I march until it's over
And just like a soldier
I keep on moving forward
Always getting closer
I march until it's over
And just like a soldier
I keep on moving forward
Always getting closer
I march until it's over
And just like a soldier
I keep on moving forward
Always getting closer
I march until it's over
It's ridiculous, I'm spitting this meticulous and limitless
While others out there spitting shit, got hits up on the charts that sit
I see why other artists quit: 'cause people don't reward good shit
They love to hate but hate to live, society you swing and miss
And honestly, I get it, promise me you won't regret it
Wasting energy, forget it, don't look back, go on get it
Bite the bullet just a bit, bite your tongue and don't say shit
Make your actions hard to miss, be a legend not a myth
It's obnoxious that I'm conscious, rapping honest
As promised, try to harness, as an artist
Stay modest, it's a long quest, I will not quit
'til ten thousand people going off when I drop this
I gotta make it now, swear to god I'm breaking out
Swear to god I'll take a bow, center stage with a crowd
'cause I got it figured out, I'm just honest and I'm loud
Staying modest but I'm proud, no, I never had doubt, yea
And just like a soldier
I keep on moving forward
Always getting closer
march until it's over
And just like a soldier
I keep on moving forward
Always getting closer
I march until it's over
And just like a soldier
I keep on moving forward
Always getting closer
I march until it's over
And just like a soldier
I keep on moving forward
Always getting closer
I march until it's over
And just like a soldier
I keep on moving forward
Always getting closer
I march until it's over
And just like a soldier
I keep on moving forward
Always getting closer
I march until it's over